{
    "id": "d357d348c5c047038403c33e933594af",
    "title": "Simple past and past perfect tense exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "030b1705e6dc4b00b75dc2db90cacafc",
            "title": "Simple Past And Past Perfect Tense Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "The patient .................................... before the doctor arrived.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "died",
                        "has died",
                        "had died"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "As the fire broke out, people ................................. out of their house.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "hurried",
                        "has hurried",
                        "had hurried"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I .................................... him yesterday.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "met",
                        "meet",
                        "had met"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I recognized him immediately as I ................................. him before.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "saw",
                        "have seen",
                        "had seen"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I wish I .................................. with my friend during his last days.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "stayed",
                        "would stay",
                        "had stayed"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "If he ................................ in time, he would have got the job.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "applied",
                        "has applied",
                        "had applied"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "By the time the firemen arrived, the fire ................................ many huts.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "destroyed",
                        "was destroying",
                        "had destroyed"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Long before the chief guest arrived, the invitees ................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "assembled",
                        "have assembled",
                        "had assembled"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I wish I .................................. my application in time.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "sent",
                        "have sent",
                        "had sent"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I did not speak to him, as I ....................................... been introduced to him.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "was not",
                        "had not",
                        "has not"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}